If you want to do two-wheeler third-party
bike insurance, then today
in this particular video we are going to
discuss how we
can do two-wheeler third-party bike insurance through CSC. We will also
know how much commission we get for this. We will
also know
how we can reprint the policy.
Let's start with this.
Friends, first of all, I will click on the insurance here and
after clicking on it, I will
click on motor third party.
As we click on motor third party, there will be
many companies here through
which we
can do insurance. Let me select one of these, for
example, if I
want to do insurance through ICICI Lombard General Insurance, then I will
click on this click here.
After clicking on this, its deal will
appear like this, as you can see, to do two-
wheeler third-party insurance,
click on this two-wheeler tip check box and then click on get.
As if clicking on gated, then its
The 10 boards will have an interface like this
as you can see and first of all
we will click on the registration number i.e. the
vehicle number here and
after flipping it we will
click on get started details like if we
click on get RTO details then some details will
automatically populate and apart from this there is
this option which you can use after reading it
then click on get and
after clicking on get,
here which will be in total free
and then click on profit and
after clicking on profit there are some
details as Shivangi as you can see
and in this there is
total premium given apart from this in vehicle
details city where the
vehicle is registered RTO and apart from this
registration number customer state first
registration date apart from this manufacturer
and apart from this policy start model and
trainer and these details are given apart from this the
engine number and chassis number are showing here we will
join it a little and
after doing this you can see
that in the base vehicle details which is board
type  Apart from this, this is noise and apart from this, we will
add a little more here, which is the
customer's details here,
let me fill this up as well,
like in the title, we
set one of these, after selecting this,
I will enter the name of this name, here I will enter the
address etc., then the postcode and
pin code, like city wise it will be
automatically filled up and apart from this, we will
fill up the email id, mobile number of the customer here
and after doing this, we will
click on generate proposal
and then here the proposal number and total
price will be put here,
then click on partner,
show more,
as you can see that the paid by
amount is 828, apart from this,
that letter mode means 770 point 25
paise, which will be detected from Amazon, like
you can take the amount above 770 point 25
paise and apart from this, the reference number is there, apart from this,
date and time are also there.  Apart from
CID and CSC password here, we will click on it,
let's click and it is done,
then we will click on bill paid
and after clicking on velvet, we will
select the last pin here
and then click on pay,
as you can see that the payment has been
successful,
as you have given here that
correlation and apart from this you have successfully
generated tap policy, please find the details
below and apart from this the total premium paid
which is 828 and apart from this the policy
number is showing here and apart from this the
policy is started over policy and at is
here and to download this and policy,
we will click on it and
after clicking on it you can see that the
policy has been downloaded finally,
as friends you can see that this
policy has finally been
downloaded in a PDF format, now we
will open it and on opening it you can see
that all the details in it will be shown
like customer's name, address,
apart from this the policy number, police start  Date
policy and apart from this, total dear and all the
details will be put in it and
you
can see it for the customer by doing this.
Friends, now we will know how to
print this Polish Corporation.
For this, friends,
click on the insurance icon here and after clicking on it,
click on Motor Third Party here and click on ICC
Lambot General Insurance click here
and after clicking on this,
its dashboard will have an
interface like this, as you can see, then
friends, click on My Transaction My Life Partner
Policy and
after clicking on this, click on From Date and
Date here, let's just do this,
like from date and
apart from this, let's take the problem
and then select Motor in Product here
and in Sub Product, for example,
select the policy for which you want to reprint it and click on Search. All these
details will be put here, as you
can see, for example, we searched for Two Wheeler
Liberty, like Police, for this reason also.
Here the customer's name,
policy number, police start date, police
pending, apart from this, the total prepaid status will be
here. Apart from this, if you
want to see the proposal, then click on it
and if we want to print another policy, then
your profile, for example, if
we want to surrender this policy, then
click on issue. You can see
that the police has been displayed in front of us, which will have an
interface like this, so that you
can download it from here and I will show you by downloading the limit. If you
want to download this file on the desktop, then this
file which has been downloaded, now we
can print it.
Now friends, let us know that for the
policy that we have
made, how much commission have we
received, for this we will click on order and vision
and click on this jersey border, this trip,
then this detail will be there,
then click on details here,
as you can see, here the
order cards are given, the
name of the service, merchant category, customer information
and what was the transaction total amount,
apart from this which  The total amount is like
how much detective money is there from our CSC wallet,
apart from this, the person who has
received commission is 60 points, they have got C
money and apart from this, tax has been levied one and a half
125 and apart from this, the tempered glass is
deducted one point 80, here as the order
number is given, in
this way friends, you
can know the commission for the policy that we have made, in
this way friends, through CSC, in
this way friends, we can make
third party bike insurance through CSC, in this way
friends, we can
make third party bike insurance through CSC,
apart from this friends, if you want to get information about CSC Central
Government Scheme and various other types
of information, then
visit our YouTube channel Increase Career
and subscribe to the channel, like,
share and definitely press the bell icon
because friends, I keep giving
latest updates on various types of information about Delhi Senior Government Scheme, see you
in the next video with the next topic,
thank you, thank you.